rehabmart.com 2017-07-22

# Privacy Policy | Rehabmart.com

The following discloses the privacy policy for Rehabmart, LLC. We take your privacy concerns seriously and we strive to earn and keep your trust. Please do not hesitate to contact us with your questions and concerns (contact information is provided below). 

We do not share any of your personal information, including your email address, with other parties. We hate spam as much as you do, so we won't give your information to anyone. 

We do not send unsolicited email. If you are receiving email from us, it is because at some point you, or someone with access to your email account, requested it. You can always opt out of any email we send you simply by following the instructions that appear at the bottom of the email message in question. If you are receiving email from us in response to an inquiry you made, you can rest assured that we will use your email address for no purpose other than to respond to your inquiry. 

We use IP addresses and cookies to help you navigate our website, to help us diagnose problems with our server, and to help us administer our website. This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

You may contact Rehabmart with questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, updating any personally identifiable information or anything else related to Rehabmart.com, LLC and/or this Site at info@rehabmart.com or by calling us at 1-800-827-8283.

##### Shop Securely & With Confidence

* * *

## Normal / Ground Shipping

**Most items** are processed within 24 hours and shipped from the warehouse within 48 hours via 3-5 day ground delivery service (unless otherwise noted). Orders placed over the weekend will be processed first thing Monday morning. We will attempt to notify you by email and provide a tracking # when your product(s) ship. 

## Freight Shipping

**Heavy items** (anything over 150 lbs), bulk-freight, palletized items and custom fabrication made-to-order items may have longer shipping lead times. Customer will be notified as soon as Truck Freight items become available for overland freight shipment.
